[Music]
greetings and a warm welcome to Chicago
as we bring you another powerful word by
Bishop Moses or no today's someone was
born in 1979 not the actual sermon by
the principles as a young Christian it
was in my first year Hawaii a Christian
I got saved 1978 the 5th of August and
then around April May of 1979 I started
having a very serious challenge I didn't
know how to deal with where I grew up
colloquially there's an altercation and
a skirmish Aleya toha between our family
and one of our the families in the
neighborhood and how it came about is
that one of the young men in the
neighborhood had a liking for my sister
he had a crush on her but instead
instead
gwenna its Rekha table he literally
stalked my sister I oppose cologne and
she only noticed afterwards that this
guy was talking here so she then told my
dad who in turn went to the father of
the boy as we do in African culture to
say ma how is talking my girl
unfortunately the mother of the boy
instead a dilettante Oh hunty she
decided to play Aloha one odium I don't
know how you say it in English to go up
with the cows and she she came up to my
mom and over the fence insulted hey you
such vulgar language that I've never had
before so here I am as a young man
coming back from school I walk in the
yard kohai and then I walk right in the
middle of this confrontation
I hate Vardar language that was great
triple-a I had never had mud or haka and
like that in my life unfortunately for
me those words almost stuck to me stuck
to my mind to an extent that wherever I
went from that day I would literally
hear these words going on in my mind in
July of 1979 I got filled with the Holy
Spirit fourth of July 1979 now I was
battling this thing because continually
in my mind I was having these words
speaking and then I remember that month
when we were praying in this house and
arabela corner one of the people I was
with said I must lay hands on one of the
ladies who was there with us praying to
pray for her to be filled with the Holy
Spirit so when I laid hands on her I
heard these vulgar words directed to her
now man you must remember my young
Christian Achatz ever what's going on
and then she didn't get filled with the
Holy Spirit and of course as I left I
was disappointed that God didn't come
through for her and immediately now I
know it's the devil at that time I
didn't know immediately there were these
words that said of course how can she be
filled with the Holy Spirit through a
debt vessel like you and then the words
went on coating Matthew chapter 12 where
Jesus was talking to the religious of
the day religious leaders of the day
where he said every blasphemy will be
forgiven even blasphemy against the Son
of God but blasphemy against the Holy
Spirit will not be forgiven and this
word said you have blasphemy the Holy
Spirit there's no forgiveness for you
you'll never go to heaven God has
rejected you and all of that now the
same thing for me is that I never
verbalized any of these words those
words were just in my head in my mind
and for three months three solid months
I battled with those words to an extent
that when I was with people with my
teachers at class as they were talking
to me the words were insulting them at
home
this thing was insulting my parents and
I didn't know what to do so I then asked
my my friends my Christian friends or
what must I do and I'll be honest with
you the advice they gave me didn't help
because some of them said pray more
those things don't get changed by prayer
look at Universal
but then one of them in an attempt
humppa advice made it worse he said you
see he had somebody era when you're a
Christian you know as you grow in the
Lord God increases your tests he said
this test is the one that's good for you
that's good but that doesn't help
thankfully I got to hear about a man by
the name of David Nunn who is an
evangelist who wrote books and I ordered
these books to higher though he used to
talk about prayer but as I checked on
the catalog I noticed that there were
other books that were there so I ordered
several books two of them in particular
one called declarations of faith the
other one called confessions of faith
when I read these books I then found out
several things I didn't know first of
all I realized that I need to look at
myself through the eyes of who I am in
Christ you see some of us even if we
have received Christ as Savior and Lord
we are be we are behaving like God
hasn't changed anything about us and
even in the way we talk about ourselves
even in the way we handled ourselves
it's almost like we are still the same
old people this is what the Bible says
in 2nd Corinthians 5:17 let's have the
scripture up on the screen it's eerie If
any man be in Christ he's a what he's
what I can tell you he's a what he's a
what then it says what all things have
done what all the alba tomb
all things have passed away and then
behold now let me ask you a question did
God mean what he said huh
and of course or did God mean what I say
old things art and what behold how many
things how many things how many things I
said how many things let's have it in
the Amplified Bible it says all things
are become new but the amplified bible
explains hurry your own moral and
spiritual condition your previous moral
and spiritual condition has passed away
so when you receive Christ the old model
life what do you mean by my own life
your sinful life you are someone who is
dead spiritually you used to do things
you were evil on the inside according to
the words of Jesus we're children of the
devil we were not born again all that is
cast away something new has happened we
are God's children is the old border
life and the spiritual life spiritually
now you're a child of God in fact in the
Old Testament moody movie where this way
or a gate lands a pillow led a guitar a
pillow a leash way in the book of
ezekiel
k trance appeal reallywe making a faint
indication pilyeon memoria it means this
heart that was evil this heart that used
to do evil and think evil and and
conjure up evil that heart we've had an
open heart surgery spiritually and God
has replaced that old evil heart from
allah wa sallam in essence once you
receive Christ
come on changes you such that you're not
only the same person now let me qualify
that doesn't mean he will not want to do
the old thing because of the film called
the flesh
which we must discipline all right so it
means when it comes to God there's no
way I can catch good there's no way I
can say evil things in my heart there's
no way because I am a changed person
I mean want to howl about this on the
inside I'm a new person that's the first
thing I learned hurry you know sometimes
the way we talk about ourselves after
were Christians we talk about ourselves
as though nothing has changed
look at your neighbor and say you are a
changed person if you have received
Christ you're a changed man the second
thing I learned is that when you receive
Christ there are certain benefits that
became yours all right good through the
death of Christ on the cross there are
things that Christ has bequeathed to us
for instance in the natural when people
are alive they write this thing called a
willow right and in this wheel bar the
day I die this thing Sena
it's about Sabina baka or whoever that's
a wheel so in Christ there's a there's a
wheel that was written I understand me
so he died on the cross and after his
death that will became ours and that
will is everything that is contained in
the Bible let me tell you how that will
is captured how it's written
all right when you read the book of
Philippians and by the way these books
are philippians colossians thessalonians
colossians elders xi'an scalable these
are the different churches of people who
are already born again these are people
have received christ and one of the
things that Paul tried to do when it
talks to born-again people is to tell
them what belongs to them
many Christians don't know what belongs
to them
see God said it in the book of habakkuk
he said my people my people are
destroyed for a lack of knowledge what
we don't know what you don't know will
destroy you
yeah so when Paul wrote to them to the
Romans the church in Rome to the
Philippians Ephesians Colossians
Colossians Thessalonians when I wrote to
Timothy when I wrote these letters when
you read these letters
Tony uses the expression in him in
Christ through Christ by Christ and how
use are these expressions he's trying to
tell you her by your receiving Christ as
your Savior and your Lord and by him
dying on the cross he made certain
benefits available for you has got many
many of these things that cover your
spiritual life if you are a child of God
spiritually you are a new creature you
are born again demonic spirits can never
come into your spirit chalo never
repellant deliverance accessible what's
wrong with you because you don't
understand who you are in Christ
spiritually you have according to
Colossians chapter 5 you have the fruit
of the Spirit that can grow in your life
they are there but you can grow them
we're not as gonna Moody all right
secondly physically the Bible says by
the stripes of Jesus we were healed
Jesus purchased divine healing for us
healing is your right
aha you're not hearing me was
it's in the will it's in the will check
your wheel check your well it says it
says it's it talks about how about the
types of Jesus you were here this
himself himself Ian Amara not just on
the cross himself took our infirmities
and bore our sicknesses and by His
stripes we were healed come on hurry up
it is alrea for this name is him boy I
can see a peaceful so healing is your
right
it's your benefit now I'm not saying
that you'll just get healed no you gotta
believe what the word says and receive
what God has given to you what about in
terms of protection God says it God says
your enemies will be my enemies he says
if your enemies come out against you one
way I'll cause them to flee before you
seven ways he says vengeance belongs to
the Lord am I talking to anybody he says
is God before you who can be against you
so I don't have to try and give up my
protection now I'm not talk about
security and all that I don't know don't
think about but there's people who go
and put things under their pillow handed
somewhere put it somewhere in the body
because Vukovar safe ah chamber -
nominally safe
because of Jesus cousin I don't have to
pay one cent to wouldn t be safe
what about in relationships God
precisely what about in your vision what
about in your mission
what about where you are going in life
he says I have plans for you yeah
Jeremiah 29:11 it says I have plans for
you plans to prosper you plans to give
you a fish I see you are not getting
excited at all time that's understood
but it doesn't mean you must stay there
are you listening to what I'm saying are
you understanding what I'm saying in
much you must learn how to apropriate
the promises of God but then I learned
something as I was reading the book of
Corinthians about the mind the Bible
says we have the mind of Christ when I
thought all right now if I have the mind
of Christ where do all these varga words
come from if I have the mind of Christ
and it's true where do all this world
always come from then I realized
something that I didn't know
Mademoiselle on the thoughts that come
into our minds have three sources three
sources number one there are thoughts
that come from you and if you're a real
born again child of God or Ottumwa demon
you wouldn't want to think bad thoughts
human secondly there are thoughts that
come from God now how do I know if that
comes from God any thought that lines up
with God's Word and it's not that agrees
with God's Word it's a thought that
comes from God God's will never give you
a thought to go and rob a bank
in the battle look at you never say yeah
I wanna Bishop arena yeah
but then there are thoughts that come
from Satan and that is why the book of
the book of Corinthians tells us to cast
down imaginations
in every thought that exalts itself
against the knowledge of God let's go to
it Caliban a Libra new worker
2nd Corinthians chapter 10 REM Kokila
once a hearing for the weapons of our
warfare are not carnal but mighty
through God to the pulling down of what
and I must learn to you I know sometimes
I work a strongholds people are talking
about demons attacking new Satan
mara these strongholds are the
strongholds of the mind according to
this verse look at the necklace earring
next verse verse 5 custom down what down
what casting down casting down
imaginations are a function of the mind
imaginations are a function of their of
the mind casting down what watch it now
and every high thing that exalts itself
against the knowledge of God so watch it
now anything that comes against the
knowledge of God where you find the
knowledge of God in the Bible
so there are imaginations that
contradict what's in the Bible and in
this verse says you need to cut them
down he didn't say pray you didn't say
pray either you must custom-done what
does it make you cast down to cast down
missed you throw down to cast down miss
just throw down you must sing so well a
thought comes when when affect enters
your mind and it goes against the
knowledge of God is that of dwelling on
it instead of thinking about it instead
of verbalizing it is that of believing
it just you don't even try you don't
even try now you don't have a driver for
sins on
casting down what image does it ever
happen that exalts itself against the
knowledge of God and bringing into
captivity every thought to the obedience
of Christ
so you must bring your thoughts into you
mustn't allow your thoughts to run wild
because these are imaginations these are
thought are against the knowledge of God
and these shots come from the devil and
this verse says that is what is involved
is what you call spiritual warfare
chasing down the most down the road no
it's dealing with the thoughts now it's
included any one murder really this
verse is talking about imaginations
thoughts so it means this man was one
man the thoughts that come to my mind I
have the responsibility to deal with
them if they are from God go to the book
of Philippians chapter 4 Philippians
chapter 4 he didn't be careful for
nothing
don't worry about anything don't worry
about anything but in everything by
prayer and supplication with
Thanksgiving let your requests be made
known unto God that's not where I'm
going I'm just going through it verse 7
and the peace of God which passes all
understanding shall keep your hearts and
minds through Christ Jesus next verse
finally brother do you have any brother
none in the house do you have any sister
any in the house
do you have any brother and sister
Anita's finally brethren whatever things
are true whatever things are honest
whatever things are just whatsoever
things are pure whatever is lovely
whatever things are of a good report if
there be any virtue if there be any
praise do what I can here into what come
on let me hear you do it so so process
what's good
everything Elmo what's true what's
honest
what is just what is pure obviously all
those things come from God these are the
thoughts that come from God he says if
this thing's dica click on that silk on
doing good than being jealous
think of giving life to somebody than
killing life let's have it in the
Amplified Bible think on these things
think on these things so in other words
it's your choice what you allow into
your mind now let me rephrase let me
rephrase let me rephrase no no no no
it's a choice what you allow to stay in
your mind
you cannot keep thoughts from coming
thoughts will come in your mind all
kinds negative thoughts positive
thoughts such from you such from God
such from the devil
they will come but as to whether how
long they stay you are the one who
determines that in the midst of a
powerful service yeah yeah yeah Kelly
boja thank you I need more of that
because you the hand-clapping is very
little these days have you ever been in
a powerful service that's very anointed
and yeah yeah worshiping Jesus
hallelujah in the middle of an anointed
service anybody knows what I'm talking
about anybody knows what I'm talking
about and you're talking about Jesus and
right in the middle of there just an
evil so just just in the in the middle
of worship in the middle or come on some
of you are a clap you're more awliya
than some of us in the middle of now
there's no way that what could be coming
from you see Satan is the one who brings
thoughts let's have that verse in the
amplified webinar every earring for the
rest brother and whatever is true
whatever is worthy of reverence and is
honorable and seemingly whatever is just
whatever is pure whatever is lovely and
lovable whatever is kind and winsome and
gracious if there be any virtue and
excellent if there is anything worthy of
praise think on anyway
and take account of these things fix
your minds on them
but then we we need to fill our minds
because this is why the battle is the
battle is in filling our minds with
wrong things that's what God told Joshua
just want it this book of the law this
book of the law this book of the law
this book of the law shall not depart
from your eyes keep it in the midst of
your heart then he says 1 meditate there
in meditate meditate means think on it
they're gonna think on it meditate on it
not just honey they are not we're a
wonderful conversation with one of my
son's yesterday and I was just sharing
with him and thank you for the
hallelujah
I demand the men are with me we are here
with the men today well yeah well yeah
and I was telling him about this concept
of taking responsibility for your life
you know what's wrong
some of you you want to live victorious
life but you you you are eating the
wrong diet spiritually I'm telling you
you know I know young people may not
like me for this but I tell them I was
young too young you think I was born
this age I was your age too and I
remember one of the things I that I
struggled with as well in this in in 79
was the effects of music Universal on a
music is very effective true
let me give you another revelation I'll
tell you why you don't appreciate it
some of you don't realize worried the
one that we call Satan now Lucifer
Lucifer he was in charge of the choir in
heaven when you read the Bible yeah he
was in charge of the choir not only that
the way God created him God created him
with music in him that's what music was
at an Illuminati soul I know you don't
want to accept that but get a boo-boo
[Applause]
yeah yeah yeah but on a music this is
what is proven this is a scientific fact
this is a scientific fact couple homily
music has the ability to go past your
conscious thinking go into your
subconscious mind deposit concepts in
your subconscious mind that you begin to
act on go and check it I'm not I'm not
I'm not telling you music can be used to
make you feel in a certain way
and to lose your defenses to lose your
defenses and lower so when you listen to
rap music hip-hop music they curse they
promote drugs sex out of marriage they
promoted Lee belly on now yes what I
want to ask you as a Christian what
business are you heavy pump bill that
stuff into your mind into your heart and
then you wonder why you are struggling
with certain things that's fine you know
that I'm not that's not gonna stop me
when I was at Bible School in the first
year that's like and I must mention it
she was a white guy who was our
colleague he used to give us a lift to a
pop-rock station because I used to study
go to Bible School at at night and our
Bible School in a fella around quarter
past eight half past eight and we had to
you know it was in run back you know a
long chance max Avenue not reform the
cuts you know those cuts in Renwick
that's where Rama used to be added for
mattoon effectors so after school would
have to quickly get to park station
because I used to commit by train so you
know every day was an event every day we
asked for a lift we had different people
transporting us but this guy for a while
he was the one who was the the constant
transport chamoy tomorrow I was in
Iqaluit you know how kopaka Sean no no
not my surname I'm just saying kiss on
that's all I'm saying one day he used to
be quiet guy very quiet very very
withdrawn and in it it was my first time
to be closely with white people I didn't
know that much I knew them from fast so
now we're in school with them we sit
next to them we are studying the same
material all of us even if really Co
felidae still apartheid is strong on
Amara we're in the same class so for me
it was a very curious time because I was
working at Rhema which was 99.999% white
so I was among white people all the time
in Suriname observing and I'm realizing
I Ramos I see you young people are
surprised at me you must ask our
generation white people were an enigma
mom only you thought that difference to
you then you find out now they eat like
me
they burp like me they go to the toilet
like me but then I started to realize in
their struggling with the same things we
struggle with this guy was required very
well quiet and reserved and he had a
look on him he was very strange very
strange there was just something he was
nice enough very handsome guy very nice
mara there was something something
something one day as he was driving he
went onto the curb
onto the side of the road I mean I
Palamon an Arab driver the old meaning
you know this no not that
Mini Cooper jets are another old mini
non I used to call it Monica and I mean
that case small when we went on the cab
we it shook the car we we hit our heads
against the roof of the car and then and
then it was like he's coming out of
something and then he said I'm sorry I'm
sorry
then you got all over and shook his head
what's going on and then the following
day he apologized he said guys I'm sorry
I'm still struggling with something that
gets hold of my mind
listen to me he said I used to practice
white magic and one of the things you do
in magic the kind he was practicing
because there's different levels of
magic there's magic where it's tricks
there's magic where it's demonic
some of you watch it on TV the demonic
one
it has certain levels where people do
things you come and people and any no
and now let me come back
let me not get distracted so then he
told us he said he he was trained how to
cast spells on people in short words
abajo ponds so the maja ponds but you
have to cooperate with them that's what
one should remain whom because in force
I do mainly I can't I can't take your
mind without your permission
you must agree with me compel my house I
know you don't like my preaching it's ok
I'm gonna just talk then he said he was
trained but what he had to do is to
allow himself to be open those of you
who opened yourself up to any influence
footage just open your mind let the
image there's a lot of energies out
there but I cannot get energy error and
it says in the process now that is a
Christian he said Satan got hold of my
Monte monic spirits get hold of my body
says there are times when I just blank
out and they control my mind so much and
I'm trying to come out of that then he
told us something that scared he said
they trained us to know how to play a
guitar in such a way that I can get you
into a state where I can cast a spell on
you and then he started telling us about
the effects of music which I had studied
before but now I'm hearing a
practitioner to remove two ovens as we
know pozzolana some of you don't
understand why we encourage you to
worship is to bring you into an
atmosphere of God
because when we start worshipping even
if 14:01 a limo to bottling because I
overtake it when you get here into a
time of worship there's something about
worship it cleanses you it's
evangelizing that's why I always tell
our musicians would have a paisa I don't
like it because they deprived us of the
privilege to have things removed from us
in the Old Testament when people who
worshiped the Bible says the glory of
the Lord filled the temple
music goes into the spirit world and
whatever powers you want to bring onto
the scene evil powers or good powers
alike so an approach in all these evil
places where they play all this music
that has feels in it that's why people
take that route so that's why our chakra
they want to go sleep with somebody you
are we all have drugs because this music
has gone into another level that's why
you'll find in this place is such an
evil presence where people in unison
know anymore how to bow Kenya in church
when does the music is playing and then
worshiping God all of a sudden the
anointing of the oh Jesus yeah after I
worship is so important we're gonna
gonna share a lot with some musicians
this coming in because I see some of
them don't get it they don't get it they
think that giving items they don't
understand the role if you read the Old
Testament the Prophet before the Prophet
could operate in their prophetic mental
they called a ministry they called a
musician because music catch you in two
lovers of spirituality you are able to
bring back their all by Jesus
so this guy said he said even if I'm
born again and I'm spirit filled I'm
struggling because my mind just goes
blank
now was enough this is a conversation
you were having with him in the car one
day in the Bible school passed away I
used to lecture then all of a sudden
passed away by the Spirit of God that's
when you know somebody is a prophet of
God by the Spirit of God he stands up
and said that guy over there and it's
the girl the same guy he says come over
here so the girl comes to the front and
then it says in the name of Jesus come
out of him and boom he goes to the
ground now you must remember oh now we
know the story behind the story no Paula
when a brother told us now I have a
friend from Malawi Stephen one stephan1
I was in class and now he didn't know he
doesn't know about their conversation
but when Pastor I prayed for this guy
God allowed him to see into the spirit
world and it says in the spirit world he
saw a big bird moves from the guy's head
and fly out of the room from that day
that guy was ok come on give God the
program somebody give God the flora
now let me explain that demon was not in
his spirit it was on his body
unison he was born again in his heart
Mara things that we've allowed can sit
on our lives more so if we haven't yet
learned how so with me when I read these
verses about thoughts then I started
making declarations of what the Bible
says about me I can cuz I have the mind
of Christ there's no way to keep
receipts I mean my parents taught has
not heard Oaxaca I mean watch once I
could walk and I know that give us a run
how the mind of Christ I'm filled with
the wisdom of God cry Caesar as I kept
on saying that and saying that in saying
that all of a sudden all that oppression
left my mind left my mind and I've been
free since today and I've learned that
the mind is the battlefield battlefield
many people don't take care of their
minds many people are careless about
what they let into their thinking
novalee is used to say this you can
never get people into victory if they
have stinking thinking and I say the
Satan will feed your mind telling you
God won't heal you there's no hope for
you you'll never be be you good you'll
never be a better person
he will tell you in your background
you'll never get out of this background
people are introduced to say open your
mind to things and some of you hmm
you get into this you get into these
things and you allow the things to come
at you and you don't realize what you're
doing
and so from today I want you to do that
verse whatsoever things are true
whatsoever things are honest
if there be any virtue think on these
things
choose thoughts that line up with the
word of God dwell on those thoughts let
me close by salon and I'm gonna pray
just now one of the things that I
learned 1979 is to place myself in an
environment of God's Word as much as
possible you notice our analytic podcast
today or CDs for those of you or tapes
for those of you but but my cell phone I
wear because I'm on a company phone I
can use data and the plan i have is to
have unlimited data but even this
morning i I was listening to a preaching
by Charles Capps
yesterday I was listening to preaching I
listen to gospel music I listen to
preaching all the time but I'm telling
you all that time all that if you find
making anyone I'm listening I've got as
portable speakers as can some Bluetooth
I've got the headphones a Bluetooth you
see me I'm because I've realized if you
pump yourself with what is good
some of it even even certain things that
you don't have the capacity to believe
for now if you keep hearing it and
hearing it and hearing it and hearing it
and hearing it and hearing it your faith
keeps growing and growing and growing
and growing and growing and growing
because faith cometh faith cometh faith
cometh faith cometh faith cometh faith
cometh faith comes Fred comes faith
comes faith cometh by hearing by hearing
not by praying not by fasting by hearing
by hearing by hearing by hearing the
Word of God faith cometh by hearing and
hearing by the Word of God that's why
when you read the Bible you know Jesus
every time you would preach and then
pray for people afterwards why because
when you preach it it raises the level
of faith so then you can pray for people
who have faith when Paul was preaching
the Bible says there was a guy who had
not worked from his mother's womb he was
in his 40s and Paul preached and he says
and perceived that the man had faith to
be healed he called him and prayed for
him that's why you what you hear was
Allen you know Jesus said it in message
mark chapter 4 he says be careful what
you hear he says take heed what you hear
but were so careless about what we
listen to
and then we wonder why our lives are not
moving forward but I believe today is
the change for your life come on give
the Lord a big hand if you give the Lord
a big hand if you believe that
come on give the Lord a big hand is the
end of you thinking wrong things and
evil things but if I was you if I was
you I would buy gospel music
I would buy CDs I would buy preaching
CDs I would I tell her I would surround
myself with it you know why because
today in this world you don't have to go
into evil things to hear them they bring
them to you I'm telling you they bring
them to your outfit a fellow who tried
this music when you go into a taxi you
hear it when you go into a shop you hear
it so try to do a spiritual detox huh do
a spiritual detox fill yourself I'm
telling you some of you your faith level
would be different your desires would be
different even your emotions would be
different if you were to just fill
yourself with wealth I talked about
purity holiness loving God faith
fidelity honesty sticking to your
marriage if you just you listen to those
kind of things na aana respect love
patience severe ends if you can listen
to that it will lift you up to another
level my goodness I see you being lifted
up to another
[Applause]
you know as Alana sometimes by not
knowing you know we get wrong advice
from people to get into some of these
beliefs and practices that really cause
damage if it is that because you didn't
know you you just you let your mind to
be influenced and maybe like that guy
you got into some of those things now
you're battling it's like a stronghold
exactly like it says like holding you
strongly now all of us will have evil
thoughts I don't know what I'm talking
about
all of us Satan will plant wrong
thoughts and we just have to throw them
down that's not a lot to come on but
there are people whose minds have been
totally taken over this is what people
don't understand about pornography you
may say no I didn't sleep with anybody
but you've given your mind
somebody somebody we kinda stayed this
way he says you know it's almost like
connecting to a sewage pipe and dumping
all the sewage into your mind and into
your spirit that's what pornography is
and you go on your own accord in the
privacy of your life and the people who
struggle with lustful thinking you you
your mind is just gone can't shake it
off you can't look at a woman and look
at her with an innocent eye
could be another areas but I'm talking
about people who are bound I've even
seen Basel on some of the many many
mental breakdowns we have these days
which has become so prevalent is because
people have yielded their minds to wrong
things people dabble
with some of the spiritual things I know
myself of certain belief systems that
have been peddled that affect young
people in their minds and because it's
all wrapped up in education sometimes
some of the education and when they
presented it looks so successful because
I was raised in it they don't know that
you as you're selling your soul selling
your soul and people are so much in
bondage that they can be relieved
there's a someone I knew years ago was a
Christian but I don't know for whatever
reason they they wanted more power
because you know these days everybody
wants my power now we see it happen even
today pastors go to some places in
certain parts of the country school ok
Ahmad mighty sark ascetic practices yeah
this man did that I didn't know I met
him I was young when I met him he had a
thing on him and he but there was
something is in shock come on now but
his influence was so much almost like
now I'm not sure what God is talking to
you in convicting you my trust on us
that this guy when you're with him
you're under a spell and he could
influence you to do things and you and
when we are young and and I never
questioned it then he was only always
hanging around young people there were
no elderly people around him and even
elderly people never went to his church
I never could understand understood
afterwards he got very ill several years
ago and I heard from someone who knew
them very close that on the last there
are last days they actually asked to be
transported to another place another
province
because they were going to see somebody
and so this person driving them was
wondering what about why one asked my
mom because my mom can't with it's a
hides yeah never multi-seat that's all
today's a highly intimate when they got
there that's my mom had passed on yeah
in how can you go he died a terrible
death I thought this only happens yeah
until I read the books of David nun who
was talking about a guy in America who
live on his deathbed was kissing God
because this guy was dipped into these
things and in the last days type of
fella hi these evil spirits would come
and strangle him and block his way cos
Aten is a is an evil master he will use
you and destroy you at the end but it
all started by people healed in it looks
so innocent you Dalek I do each aboard
with a lock entertain our heads are so
you just play around this manana games
you don't realize you're opening your
mind I'm not saying you have demons but
I'm saying whatever bondage God wants to
break the Spirit of the Lord is upon me
he has anointed me
to preach the gospel to the poor he has
sent me to heal the brokenhearted that
word brokenhearted has to do with the
psychological realm and that's because
of their 19th well that's where we leave
it for today we hope you are blessed by
this awesome work for more information
on where you can find a crazy bubble
church near to you please visit our
website using the details on the screen
feel free to interact with us using our
various social media platforms until
next time god bless